Isaac!
It is time, ladies and gentlemen.
The day is upon us.
From now on, I will never again die.
We shall reach winstreaks of tens, twenties, thirties, hundreds of wins in a row.
No more mistakes.
I am tired of losing.
BOOM!
Let's hope that holds up.
We'll have to see.
Cheers.
We have to celebrate the start of a new era.
I'm drinking iced tea.
I have become addicted to sugar-free iced tea lately.
For some reason.
I drink so much of it and I gotta go pee all the time.
It runs right through me.
No, but I'm serious.
We have been losing way too much.
And it's time to stop.
And actually win.
No more sucking.
I've played this game for, wait, how many hours?
A hundred and seventy-six hours.
At this point, I should be winning every run.
And every time I don't, it's a failure.
Maybe challenges today.
We'll see.
You're off the coke?
I've been off the coke for a while.
Oh wait, that sounded wrong.
The way I said that.
Coca-Cola, okay?
I haven't been drinking Coca-Cola for a while.
Come on.
Oh man, this music is getting me freaking hyped.
To play some, uh...
Fuck, what's the game called?
Ark Raiders again.
I've actually been missing it.
I've been missing some kind of online game.
Maybe, uh...
What's it called?
Not Deadeye, not Deadbolt.
Uh, the freaking Valve game.
Deadlock.
That one.
Okay, anyway.
Let me, uh...
Switch this over.
Here we go.
Isaac.
Isaac, my sweet boy.
What I didn't tell you, by the way.
Yes, we're gonna win every run.
But I'm gonna be playing only overpowered characters.
Hey, I gotta try and win somehow, right?
We're going back to basics.
Nah, I'm kidding.
But I will play...
Isaac.
It's all about Isaac.
We're playing Isaac.
Oh, I guess we're not.
Hold on, we're already in the middle of a run.
You know what?
We take those.
I believe.
What was I doing?
I am a BB.
And I got Poops.
And I believe.
I believe we can make it.
Um, let me move my mouse pad out of the way.
I'm gonna be playing so smart today.
Like, literally, so smart.
If I lose, it's not my fault.
It's someone else's fault.
Wait, why am I doing so much damage?
Okay, 3.67 damage is not that much.
I mean, it's okay, but...
Nothing crazy.
We got a potato peeler.
Isn't that what that is?
It is.
I really ought to be donating some more.
I bet there's something really good that happens at a thousand.
Right?
Maybe all shops from now on are half price.
Imagine if that's actually what it is.
That would be game-changing.
Get away from me.
Excuse me.
Okay, we got him.
Keep looking for tinted rocks.
I don't see any.
That's just mean.
Oh my god.
Don't panic.
Take care of the flies.
Run.
Sniper.
That's what they call me.
Like, this is a crazy room, isn't it?
It's a tough one.
I handled it pretty well.
Da-da-da-da.
Come on.
I feel like I've never seen these enemies.
Like this enemy right here.
Or maybe it's just really rare.
Bob's Curse.
That means we can go get a key.
I do like that.
And I'm immune to poison, right?
Yes.
Lovely.
Hey, yo, where's that upgrade that lets me heal with bombs?
I haven't seen that in a while.
Oh wait, I forgot about a treasure room.
How the hell did I forget that?
What is actually wrong with me?
How does that happen?
Roid Rage.
Okay.
Let's see if we can get spun.
Spun out of our minds.
High on drugs.
Stimpaks.
There's definitely no stepping today, but I just want to have a peek.
Okay.
I've had my peek.
Love peeking.
We could actually bomb to look for secrets.
We got some bombs here.
Five bombs.
That looks doable.
What about the other side?
Let's have a look.
Looks good to me.
That is just a great start.
You want keys?
You're not getting it.
Nope.
We could look for another secret.
Where, though?
I don't know.
Fast time.
Also, today, we're actually gonna do angels.
Demons are forbidden today.
If I accidentally do a demon, it's accidentally.
Like, it's never gonna be on purpose.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let me kill your people.
Your daughters and your sons.
I will murder them all.
Oh, God.
Oi!
I ran into the little piece of shit.
Literally.
Okay.
That's good.
He's very tanky, isn't he?
Okay.
Killed the little guy.
Another charge.
Just like that, huh?
No problem.
I did lose a little bit of HP, but it happens.
Wait.
Hold on.
What's happening?
Oh, it's Jackie.
She likes to scratch after she's done eating.
Scratch things, you know?
Let's go!
Wonderful.
I would say that's a solid first floor.
100% demon, but we're not going demon.
No.
Fly, stay back.
Stay back.
Ah, they shouldn't be attacking enemies.
I want to save them for bigger enemies.
Yeah.
Kill flies first.
I need to have some sort of, um...
what do you call it, hierarchy in my brain.
Telling me which enemies to focus, you know?
Some enemies are more dangerous than others.
Okay.
Lure them into a corner.
And now I'm in a corner!
Fuck.
I lured myself into a corner.
Hey, look at this!
Very nice.
Our mistake has been undone.
E.
coli.
Wait, that's two out of three on...
Oh, crap, then.
What happens on three out of three?
I have no clue.
Something about poop, obviously.
You can't follow me!
That's poop!
Ha ha ha!
Poop obstacle!
Or a poopstacle.
Okay, so we have a bunch of poop here.
I'm gonna save that.
But when we get to a boss area...
Oh, wait, he just got turned into a poop.
Common collected.
Now we grab the rest of this.
We're gonna get so many flies for this boss.
It is actually glorious.
Only six coins, though.
Okay, never mind.
Eight.
Do we want to go to our shop, is the question?
I don't think so.
Okay, flies versus flies.
Get him.
Good amount of damage.
Get away from me.
Nice.
Boom!
Squeezy!
That is huge, man!
More HP is so important for me.
Okay, uh...
Eight coins.
Let's really play this smart.
We're not taking demons, obviously.
Let's look for secrets.
This is not a secret, because there's a jar.
It could be in here.
Yeah, that looks clean.
Left side clean.
What about top part?
Clean.
Do it.
I'm so good at this game.
Uh, what is that?
Isn't that Monster Manual?
I want it.
No, it's Necromonicon.
Um...
Hmm.
Do I even want that?
I guess I do.
Yeah, it's fine.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I should have destroyed this rock!
Look at that!
It's freaking marked.
Whoops.
That was a mistake.
Kind of want to blow these guys up as well.
I mean, there's four of them.
They're just begging for it.
Okay, I want that.
Give me the coupon, man.
And now we go to the shop!
Well, we haven't found it yet, but it should be over here.
So these are little ticks, I guess.
Little...
Bastards carrying diseases.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Nice.
Oh my god, how am I even supposed to dodge that?
Okay, not bad.
I handled that.
I'm not intrigued by this.
Voodoo Head spawns an additional curse room.
The problem with that is, I only have blue hearts, and every single piece of heart is so valuable to me.
But, I mean...
D'ah!
Hey!
Ah!
I didn't want that anyway.
Let's leave.
All in all, I would say...
Wait, what am I doing?
Wrong way.
All in all, I would say...
Oh, was that a...
No.
Anyway.
All in all, I would say...
Wait, can I actually pick this up?
No.
I can only have blue hearts.
I can't have any other hearts, right?
Let's go here.
Cheers, guys.
There we go.
Angel chance has been...
Achieved right now.
These are like golden poops.
Or like golden poop nuggets.
Dude, what?
Insane enemies.
Fishtail.
When blue flies are spawned...
Oh, no.
I should have kept my poop.
Imagine.
Ah, man.
That's just unfortunate.
It really is.
Imagine all the flies I could have had.
Are you imagining it?
Now double that amount.
That's how many flies I could have had.
That's crazy.
Sir.
There we go.
Wee-wee.
Ne-ne-ne-ne.
Down here.
This is where they grow tomatoes.
Stop that.
More bombs?
Can't wait to get to a shop and use my coupon.
Come on.
What?
Did you see the way he fucking flew at me at light speed?
I've never seen anything like that.
What was that just now?
That's new.
I had no chance of avoiding that.
Nope.
Ooh.
Good thinking there with the shooting it.
Good job, me.
Watch.
Perfection.
Oh, actually not bad.
Very nice.
There's the shop.
No, wait.
That's the treasure room?
Also very good.
I just can't wait to get to a shop, because I want to use my battery charges right now, you know?
It's kind of wasted at this time.
Stigmata.
Ooh, damage.
Very nice.
More damage is good.
Wait, what?
What hit me?
I'm so confused.
I thought I dodged everything.
There's a skeleton coming out of that, I guarantee it.
Why are they not dying?
What the fuck?
They have so much HP.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there they are.
Oh, no.
I'm leaving.
Come on, then.
What are you doing?
This is a killer room.
Rainbow poop.
That's the one that heals.
Shop.
Are you ready?
No, it's shit items.
No.
Why you gotta do this to me?
You know what?
Donate.
No.
Keep him.
For now.
Keep the money.
Wow.
How did I do that?
I'm amazing.
There's a fight room we missed, but it's okay.
Hey, look.
I picked up the same thing that this guy is.
Or I could have picked it up.
I wonder what happens then.
I'm gonna blow them up.
Get poisoned, nerd.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oi, oi, oi.
Actually solid.
Yeah, I did that pretty well.
Mr. Dolly is amazing.
Come on, blue hearts.
Yo!
Lucky me.
That is incredible.
Very nice.
No angel, though.
No angel.
Can't do it.
Free hot dogs for life!
No drinks.
Can't do it.
Six, seven angel.
What are these things doing?
Looks like that guy is constipated or something.
I heard the whew!
It's a sign.
Oh.
I'm not sure what the deal is with those poops.
Like, what is the point?
It's odd, isn't it?
Yeah, come at me.
Ahoy!
Another blue heart!
What the fuck, dude?
It's going so well.
Precise inputs right there.
I'm not gonna take that.
Oh, what the?
Kill this little guy.
He's annoying me.
No!
That was terrible.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah!
Nice.
No, it's not even a real shop!
I'm getting so unlucky right now.
Like, this coupon is just useless.
Wait a sec.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a sec.
Maybe this would be the one time Devil Rooms are preferable.
It makes them free.
You know?
Too late for this now, anyway.
But we're going, Angel.
We're gonna stick to the...
I was about to say script, but...
The plan.
Let's just say the plan.
Oh!
Wait, oh no, we can't see items.
Okay, well...
Rub it in, will you?
Give me all the best...
deals in the world, and never offer a shop to me.
How about that?
That's like telling me I have infinite...
free burger vouchers at McDonald's.
But there's no more McDonald's.
Great.
I heard the whale again!
Good.
Ah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Losing a bit too much HP here for no reason.
We haven't found treasure room yet, either.
I can't let that stand.
Oh, yeah, this is safe.
Actually, you know what?
I'm doing this.
Nothing.
Uh...
Okay.
Nice.
That's just...
infuriating.
Dude, dude, dude, dude!
Ay-yi-yi.
Here we go.
Piggy bank.
Even more money for the shops I'm never getting.
Yeah!
Okay, the one thing that could happen that would be really great is a shop where I can re-roll.
That needs to happen at this point.
It just has to happen.
Stop spawning these little bastards!
Please!
Oh!
Get out of there!
Wow.
Scary.
At this point, I kind of just want to go into that curse room.
Fuck it.
I'm doing it.
Let's see if it's worth it.
Watch this be a sprinkler.
You ready?
Hey!
Okay!
I am so happy.
Good shit.
But we only have four hearts now.
Oh, wow.
More money.
Steam sale and a coupon?
I mean...
Bring on the shops, is all I'll say.
In fact, imagine a shop where I can keep buying blue hearts.
That would be the ideal situation, right?
Mega fatty.
Oh, god!
I'm actually so scared of this guy.
Oh!
I'm gonna jump again!
That was fast!
Oy!
Keep mo- Okay, okay.
You're doing that.
Gotta jump!
Okay.
And...
Go!
No!
Okay.
He's doing that.
That's cool.
Come on, angels!
Angels!
Be good to me!
Angel me!
Yes!
Toothpicks?
That's actually pretty good for me.
Okay.
Let's see what we get.
No!
Imagine, man!
Imagine I didn't have question marks!
What if I use a coupon in here?
It was just a test.
Habits.
Item martyr.
That is just fucking terrible, dude.
What a shit angel!
And this is what I gave up two demon rooms for?
Four?
Possibly three!
Oh my god!
Yeah, it's not looking good.
It's all of a sudden pretty bad.
Two and a half hearts and nothing to show for it.
Not great.
We still have a bit of an angel chance here.
Why?
Nice.
Oh no, not this room.
Like, this room is just utter insanity.
Low map!
Damn!
I think I want to go straight to the boss.
I want another angel.
And I need it now.
Oh no, what's going on here?
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh my god!
Fucking coupon your ass!
Toi!
My god, he's fast!
I think I'm down here.
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
I'm totally dead.
There's no way.
I win this.
Oh!
Gimme!
Oh, not the bandages!
Go suck!
A duck!
I'm so unlucky.
That's what this is.
Oh my god!
Focus!
Ah, we're cooked!
I mean, fucking take me out back and shoot me in the head.
Fucking hate this character.
We're going Isaac, baby!
Yeah.
No more fucking around with BB.
I didn't even want to play BB.
It was just because I was, you know, in that run.
And I wanted to continue it.
From now on, the first time doesn't count, remember?
From now on, we never lose again.
Because from now on, we're only playing good characters.
You're gonna bomb me?
Yeah, I'll go this way.
Let's see if we actually get items worth re-rolling this time.
Or if I'm gonna end up liking every item.
That always happens on Isaac.
Ha ha ha!
Okay, dude.
Fucking jumping from Africa.
Right into my face.
At light speed.
Come on.
No, you can...
Stop spawning these guys.
I don't like it.
I think they only spawn little guys when they're scared and running away.
I'm not sure though.
Actually, no, I'm gonna save that heart until I lose more HP.
This is how much I'm gonna optimize today.
And jump at me.
Good.
Uh, okay.
This shouldn't be a problem.
Oh my...
I thought that was the boss.
It was just his little minion.
I was like, I know where he is.
Oh, there you are.
Are you gonna spawn more minions?
Oh my god.
If I don't win a single run today, I'm uninstalling the game.
Like, I'm done with Isaac.
Then I'm simply just not good enough for the game.
You know what I mean?
If that happens today, I will be done.
I have to win at least one fucking run today.
Like, I can't believe this, you know?
It's too much.
I'm going in here.
Only good decisions now.
It's already paying off.
The chariot is good.
Dude!
Okay, this is looking very good.
And we can re-roll.
Let me destroy all these first before I think.
I can't think with these active.
Fucking hit it.
There we go.
Okay, so we have this thing is shit.
This thing is shit.
This thing is decent.
But also shit.
I'm going to re-roll.
Bro.
This is some bullshit.
I'm taking...
Wait, dry baby.
This is actually a really good one.
Because it really does output a lot of damage.
Ghost baby.
Death's list is good.
But it's also dangerous because it makes me play bad, you know?
But let's take it.
I'm taking these two.
Yep.
That's the plan.
I should have taken the card.
I didn't.
I don't know why I didn't.
It's a mystery.
Nobody will know.
There's actually a real deep meaning behind me not taking that.
I will not reveal it though.
But it's really smart why I didn't do it.
You'll see what I mean in approximately 17 minutes.
Watch this.
Plus one HP.
Okay, well that's not bad either.
Good with some luck here.
Move on.
All right, we're gonna really abuse this death's list now.
But only in rooms where it makes sense.
If it looks bad, I'm not gonna do it.
It looks good.
Maybe.
We gotta get behind him.
Yeah, we hit him.
We hit him.
Sniper.
Good attempt though.
Okay, this is not happening.
It ain't happening.
I will bait these guys into me.
If I can.
I can.
Okay.
Come at me.
So far the rooms have not been good for the death's list.
This is also not gonna happen.
Maybe?
Okay, maybe this is gonna happen.
Yes.
Solid.
Nice.
It's looking good.
Bomb bag.
That's horrible, man.
I may re-roll that.
I'm not gonna pick it up yet.
What does it say?
Drops a bomb pick up every three rooms.
Yeah, no thanks.
I'm good.
Ah, don't kill him.
Ah, stupid fly.
Why'd you have to go ahead and do that?
Where are these flies coming from?
Push.
I'm losing my patience.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
2.5 range for free.
That's what we need to do.
Every single room.
Imagine if that was damage up, though.
Okay, this room is some bullshit.
That's not happening.
Not doing death's list in here.
I have my limits.
But it could have been, like, plus damage, maybe.
Okay, we have a full re-roll now.
But there's gonna be a demon in here.
And I really wanna go in there and re-roll that.
I know I said no demons today, but we already took a demon because we took the card, so I don't have a choice.
Okay, this is the demon run.
But before I go in, maybe I wanna collect some more hearts.
Or actually go re-roll this thing!
Yeah, let's go re-roll...
If I re-roll this...
Will I be able to get enough battery for another re-roll?
Probably not.
Let's go see what's there.
Maybe it's good, you know?
Let's see what the demon has to offer us.
Okay, big guy first.
No!
Stop it!
Come on.
How come the little dry baby isn't producing room-wide damage right now?
Didn't they just run into him?
Like, look, he's right on top of him.
Okay, now it's the li...
What was that?
He cut me off at the corner.
That cheese-configurated nerd.
Wait, why did two item spawn just now?
Oh!
It's from death's list?
So wait, does this mean I can pick up both?
That's crazy.
I'm taking this.
Oh, fuck.
Never mind.
That's not what it means.
But I wanted this anyway for the demon.
Money equals power or brimstone bombs?
I hate them both.
Give me a brimstone.
Attack.
Okay, well, that's not too bad.
But it is actually pretty bad because that's all my heart's gone.
Bloody lust.
Grants a stacking damage bonus each time I take damage.
Ew.
Ah.
No.
Oh, shit.
Alright.
Mission now is to get some actual red heart containers.
So we can fill them up with red hearts.
And, uh, on the plus side I look like a Jedi now.
So there's that.
You know what?
Just fucking donate my money.
I'm not gonna be able to buy anything anyway.
This is one of those runs where you're poor, the game has just decided it from the get-go.
You will never get money.
Either you're fully rich or you're fully poor, you know?
What's that word?
For the difference between really rich people and really poor people.
Whatever that word is, we have a lot of it right here.
Inequality.
Chabayo!
Maybe I shouldn't go for it!
Just for it to fail.
Come on, health up!
Never lucky.
I am blessed with bad luck in this game.
That's a fact.
Huh?
Oh, the baby got hit.
Okay, so who's on my list?
Who is naughty?
Who is not?
You are on my list!
Ah, well, that ruined it all.
Yeah, that's kind of impossible.
Nice.
Yoink!
This way.
I need some easy rooms where I can use my list.
That is my way to get back, you know?
Here we go.
It's a good room.
Health up!
Hematemesis.
Ah.
Huh.
Interesting.
So Hematemesis just produces a bunch of red hearts when you don't have any red hearts.
Nice!
Plus one damage!
There we go!
The list is making it happen.
This could be another plus one damage.
It could be another plus one damage!
Get the bomb, get the bomb.
Nice!
Kill this little worm!
I'm actually a gamer.
Come on, that counted, right?
I killed the bomb first, the bomb killed the other guy.
How did that not count?
Nah, bro, that's bullshit.
Absolute bullshit.
After that performance right there, I deserve praises and medals.
Okay, let's kill this guy first.
Who's next?
It is you!
No!
Wait, he's in the fire.
Okay, okay.
Uh, yes.
Let me in.
Health up!
Okay, that's good too!
That's very good.
What is that?
Uh, lost cunt.
Ooh, uh...
Yes!
I actually like that one.
Small chance of spawning a blue spider when I'm in a room with enemies.
Okay.
May as well.
Nice!
We got some shot speed.
That's big.
I wonder if the death list has already paid for itself.
You know, if you actually combine all the upgrades I've gotten.
Now, obviously I'm gonna buy that pill.
Health up.
Okay!
I'm lucky now!
Good luck!
This one's gonna be a bit tough to do, but I'm gonna try.
Did I mess it up?
I messed it up.
I'm not sure how, though.
I killed the right guy.
Yeah, this guy.
Who's next?
I see you, I see you.
Yeah, yeah, nice!
Good!
Who's next?
Uh, you!
I see you!
No!
We messed it up.
I actually like the contact.
Because it destroys their projectiles, and that's really nice.
Plus damage, come on!
Oh, it's just a key.
Uh, yeah, let's go.
What was that sound?
Jesus!
Whoa!
I can just stand here.
I destroy his projectiles.
I'm chilling.
Stay mad.
No!
Nah, bro.
I'm back to being unlucky.
This is...
I'm...
Never lucky.
Oh, my God.
That's the sound of my bones breaking.
Hey!
Ringworm.
Uh, I'm always getting baited by this item, but not today.
I will not get baited.
This one's gonna be a little tricky.
Can we even...
Oh, God damn it.
The answer's no.
Oh, wait.
This is really good.
I need to have this.
Spokers are amazing.
Whoa!
Robo Baby 2.0.
Worked out all the kinks?
Familiar whose movements are controlled by the attack buttons?
Automatically fires lasers at enemies in its line of sight.
Huh.
Interesting.
I feel like they have not worked out all the kinks.
This feels weird.
I would call this kinky.
Definitely.
One down.
No, my guy killed another fucking sabotage.
I can't stand sabotage.
Health up.
Okay, actually, that's good.
I like being a little larger again.
Ah.
I do enjoy.
Blow him up.
Nice.
A bit more demon chance.
This could be the deciding factor.
And we get free entrance to here.
Which is also kind of nice.
Um, I may...
Don't exit via there.
That would be a mistake.
This one's gonna be impossible.
Yeah.
Enemies like this, it's just almost impossible to...
To list, you know?
It is a dream of mine, though, to list one of those guys one day.
Okay.
It's always the inanimate objects, isn't it?
Good.
Once again, we have sabotage.
Got traitors in our midst.
I think this coin is actually the reward for the list.
Get him!
Oh!
Huh!
Oh, okay.
Some more range?
Okay.
Not too shabby.
Okay, we've got money this time around.
Oh!
Is that...
Smelter!
The thing is, though, I would love to keep my D6.
So, it's a problem.
It's a problem.
Is it, though?
Is it a problem?
Maybe it's alright.
I'm gonna use it now to smelt this.
We're gonna save up for a battery and smelt another item.
I'll be back.
We also have nine bombs to find potential second secret room.
There's potential.
Oh, this guy wants...
You know what?
Let's give him some.
I know you're angry.
I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
There you go.
You would think he loves explosions, right?
Bobby bomb.
Place bombs gain a homing effect.
That is pretty good.
The thing is, though, I could re-roll this.
But there's a 72% chance of a demon being able to re-roll in there is also great, right?
I'm gonna re-roll.
Thunder thighs.
One health!
There we go.
And we get to break things.
Now I'm just gonna charge this up with a battery.
And we are ch- No!
I didn't mean to destroy him.
The baby is ruining my life.
There's definitely kinks to be worked out on this one.
We need a robo-baby 3.0.
I just lost a lot of HP.
I just realized I shouldn't have gone in here.
Yeah, I'm- I'm getting- I'm trying to control this baby at the same time.
It's not happening.
A quarter.
That is not gonna stay open, is it?
If I leave now, it's gonna close.
Shit.
I gotta get in there.
Ah, never mind.
It's a- I can't even choose anyway.
A lump of coal.
Better than nothing.
They do increase in size a little bit, so it helps.
And my tears are now poop-shaped.
And poop-colored.
Let's go back.
Wasn't there another, uh, trinket we had somewhere?
Trinket- I think up top?
We can definitely smelt that.
Uh, not this one.
Terrible trinket.
This one.
Yep.
I'm gonna smelt that.
This way.
I feel kinda slow, though.
I need more speed.
I don't know why I only have 0.75 speed.
What did I do to deserve this?
Let me get this one.
Smelt!
Dude, I kinda wanna keep the smelter.
Is that crazy?
Like, I feel like it's almost better than the D6.
The D6 is nice, but I almost always end up finding good items anyway, you know?
I'm also gonna buy this.
Wheel of Fortune.
Uh...
Ah...
Okay.
Oh, Joker!
Wait a sec, wait a sec.
There was no devil room, right?
Wait...
Can we make a sh- Can we make a play here?
Let me think.
Wheel of Fortune.
How much energy do I have on this?
I need two bars?
There's a fight room!
Maybe it's open.
Let me have a quick look.
Let me see here.
Damn.
Okay, that's not happening then.
I don't think we can get the battery.
Nah, it's okay.
Ah, maybe blow this up.
Oh, wait!
I can rock through it!
Health up!
Nice!
Soul hearts are great!
Isn't that what the tiger says, Tony?
Okay, I- I, uh...
We can also buy that heart.
I may actually do it.
Little boy to the table or angel room.
No, actually, I'm gonna keep this and go to the next floor.
That's the play.
But I'm gonna take this and double my coins.
And then we have this one.
I'm gonna blow that up together with the guy hanging.
Nice.
I could also check out what this card is.
Another Wheel of Fortune.
I didn't mean to...
Okay.
Load up.
We have the stars.
Eh...
Magician.
Magician is also good.
But I'm keeping this.
Then I'm buying that.
And then I'm taking...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, take this.
I'm taking the Smelter!
I believe in the Smelter play!
You can call me crazy.
I'm leaving behind the...
D6, baby.
This is the real deal.
Like, this is cumulative...
Power you can acquire, you know?
It's worth a lot.
Yeah.
Good.
Now we just gotta find a bunch of trinkets.
And it's gonna get crazy.
Like, with this darkness, I don't think death's list is gonna happen here, unfortunately.
Huh?
Aha!
Look at this!
How's that gonna work?
Wait, how's that gonna work with Smelter?
I wonder.
Huh.
Oh!
There's an enemy.
And list is ruined.
Thank you, baby!
Once again.
Oh, battery?
I only have one key, though.
So, mom's toenail...
We have to actually physically drop the item.
So...
I don't even see how that could work.
With this thing.
Oh, man.
Stupid baby's ruining it all.
Just kill him.
Is he shooting something like this?
Yo, the baby's actually kinda nuts.
Because I can sit in a corner and just run him around like this.
Champion belt!
I do like that!
Yoink!
Thanks.
I want trinkets, though.
More trinkets.
Not gonna go in there.
It can be lucrative to go in there.
Hmm.
How am I actually gonna get across there?
I'm not.
Wait, this guy's invisible?
Wait, I have an idea.
Check it out.
And now, who's next?
This guy?
So, we walk the baby like this?
This is some next-level shit.
No!
Oh, no.
He...
He ruined it all.
I'm gonna try it on the toenail.
The toenail has now been ingested.
Hehehe, ew.
What does it mean?
Maybe it doesn't do anything.
What if I hold control now?
Oh, right.
Okay.
I mean, maybe, you know, the foot would come down.
Who knows?
We have good damage?
Like, we're doing pretty okay here.
Oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi, oi.
I'm gonna walk into every rock.
Just in case there's, like, a...
A trapdoor, right?
Boss already?
Uh...
Yeah.
Okay.
But hold on.
So, I didn't use my joker yet.
I wonder what's best.
If I enter the boss room now, without using the joker...
There's a chance I can get...
A devil room, right?
On my own.
And if I can't, then I use the joker.
That's the way to do it.
I will never fall for that laser attack again.
Maybe I even bait the laser attack a little bit.
Like this.
Yeah, he was about to do it.
Okay, so look.
We have no devil room.
So I take this, and then I go there now.
Boom.
That's so smart.
I think this is an easy decision.
We take the ocular rift.
That's not bad.
Now, I could also take this, but I'm not going to.
I decided against it.
Treasure room, not been found yet.
And where's all my trinkets at?
I was hoping to be showered with trinkets.
And what is this?
What do I get?
Oh, God.
Boy.
Well, the smelter is ready.
Dude, this little robo baby is actually kind of good.
Two red hearts.
Okay.
Yes!
Massive.
Aha.
Oh, oh, I don't have any red hearts left.
That's too bad.
Yeah, we permanently have the booger effect now, because we smelted that.
We're actually kind of strong.
Yeah, get him, get him.
And then this guy.
Beautiful.
Nothing else.
Let's destroy these.
What if there's like a rule, where the trap door can only appear like in the center of a room, you know?
That's gonna take us conjoined, baby!
Mega.
Mega massive.
Now we're really cooking.
There's no way I can lose this run at this point.
I'm calling it now.
This is just unlosable.
Destroy everything.
Very good.
Clean.
Don't even care about the list.
Okay, I'm definitely going in here.
Wait, is it gonna increase my chances of black hole spawning?
Because I shoot way more tears.
Oh, man, that makes it even better than I thought.
What was that?
Mom's Pearl?
Yeah!
We're gonna...
Smelt that!
Feels good, yo!
Do we look for secrets?
There's one right here.
Look, look, look.
Right here.
Okay, just kidding.
There could have been one.
Let's get out of here.
After checking all these out, of course.
Can I really not get in there somehow?
Okay.
The fool.
Very good.
Don't want to blow myself up.
Oh, man, I can't believe I'm actually winning.
This is so huge.
This is the start of a big change.
The first of many wins.
This run will go down in the history...
Of my own history.
Of the run that changed everything.
You know?
I need more trinkets.
I am not satiated.
It's so satisfying to destroy all this.
Careful.
Wow, nothing in here at all?
Under these rocks?
That's surprising.
Oh, man.
I thought I could hit four at a time.
Get him.
No!
You sabotager!
I hate you.
Yeah, the baby's actually ruining the list.
Completely.
Oh, by the way, we have the fool.
We could go home.
I think I'm gonna do it.
Do I?
No, I don't.
Blow it up, maybe?
Nice!
Wait.
Oh, I can't go in there.
Brother!
There we go.
Not sure if that was worth.
Maybe.
Ah, I killed the wrong guy.
Smelter is ready.
Now to find a trinket.
Another blue heart.
It's looking almost too good to be true here.
Let me in.
I think it's a bug that it's not showing what's happening with this, but it's a good one.
Like, it should show.
Yeah, fuck that coin.
I'm gonna let the baby take care of him.
Look!
I'll take a steam sale.
But there's not gonna be any more shops.
Well, not that many.
If any.
Strength?
No.
I keep my pool.
Be a good one.
Oh, not that one.
Okay.
That was nice.
I'll say that.
Good to know.
Battery.
Uh...
I mean, we can use it to get another card.
If we want to.
Or we blow this guy up and get some...
Demon.
Yep.
Now, there's a chance we find two trinkets, right?
That battery can help with that.
Let's actually engage the...
The gambling mode.
769.
Oh, wait!
That's a donation machine!
Ah, okay.
You know what, actually?
Yeah, why not?
Fill it up.
I've been taking too much lately.
It's time to give back.
Yeah.
Oh, wrong way.
That was strength.
Strength.
Kill this guy first.
Oh, no.
Impossible.
Another fool!
I feel like every time I destroy one of these hats, I get a fool.
Is that just me imagining things?
Or maybe it's just very unlucky or lucky, depending on how you look at it.
See, that was lucky.
Okay, so we have the fool.
Are we ready?
Let's go.
Mom!
I'll show you what's good.
I'm actually an expert at killing Mom at this point.
That is one thing I can do.
I am good at that.
That was pretty good.
I like it.
We even have demons.
So, I don't think any of these are good.
Let me just have a look.
Dark Bomb.
Consumes red hearts.
Oh.
I mean, for me, that's good right now.
Dark Matter.
Oh, that one's good.
I'll take that.
In fact, I'll take both.
Ah, but let's be careful.
If I take this, I can easily see myself going down to two hearts, and then the run is over.
But!
There is a lot of red hearts scattered around this level.
Maybe we can turn those into black hearts.
I believe.
It's gonna be good.
You'll see.
So, when I said there was a lot of hearts scattered, I meant one, apparently.
Gosh dang it.
I, for some reason, I remember there being a lot more.
Good.
That already made my mistake.
One third less.
Bad.
I'll take the Strength card.
Thank you very much.
That one.
I don't want that.
Take it.
Produce for me a black heart.
Poop it.
Oh, oh!
Don't go that way!
Don't go in there!
Oh, man.
I almost did it.
Imagine.
That would be so foolish of me.
Should we...
No, we should not.
Don't be tempted.
Time to leave.
There's a chance.
Dang.
It's fine.
The run is good.
We can't lose.
I told you.
There's gotta be, like, at least one trapdoor here.
Somewhere.
I knew you were gonna laser me.
I'm afraid of this thing.
Oh!
You're fast!
I keep forgetting how fast you are.
Little son of a gun.
Wait, what?
Oh my god.
What?
Who's alive?
Oh, it's you.
I hate this room.
Kill it.
What did we get?
Oh, a key.
Oh, no.
Wait, what if I destroyed this?
Oh, cool!
Check that out!
I didn't know that could happen.
That's awesome.
Wait, we actually found the boss.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Oh, was that a shop?
Box of friends.
What about a trinket?
Oh, give me this.
Definitely.
There's a re-roll now and I don't have any money!
Man.
It's so cheap as well.
Maybe I'll find some more money.
Go!
Oi!
I almost messed it up.
Part of me regrets the smelter play.
But only a small part of me.
A large part of me still thinks it's good.
Sick.
We actually got the list going.
Get up!
Why are you not hitting- Oh, I see.
No way- No, I don't have any money!
Beelzebub.
I'll be back.
I need money first.
Surely we can find some money down here.
Wow.
Oi!
Okay.
No trinkets in sight, huh?
I'm trying to do the list.
But it's not working.
Oh!
Give me a black heart.
This guy hasn't pooped a single black heart yet.
I'm disappointed.
He has not been worth it.
These ones I cannot dislodge.
Ah, is that a shwoop?
I mean, at this point, maybe it's worth it.
I'll take it.
Fuck the smelter.
We're not getting any trinkets anyway.
I'd rather be able to shwoop.
Okay, we got two coins.
We could potentially re-roll.
Or we destroy the machine and re-roll that way.
Okay, let's re-roll normally.
Oh, wait a second.
I need to get in there.
No.
Oh my...
Yeah!
Stupid-ass game.
Nah, it's over.
We can't win this run.
I told you.
From the beginning.
Spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
Oh, shut up, Dad.
Hey!
How could you have spent our...
Savings?
Uh...
Why not?
Yeah!
Ah, but hold on.
We still have an issue here.
And the issue is...
If we are...
If we don't find the key...
Then we can't even unlock character, right?
So we're actually kind of reliant on RNG right now.
I forgot about that.
But that's okay.
You can't win if you don't take the chance, right?
Okay, he's gonna pick those up and poop out for me.
Black heart, black heart!
Yes!
One more.
Uno mas!
No uno mas?
I have bad feelings about...
I'm getting, you know, bad aura in here.
That room is not great.
Beautiful!
Huge!
Okay, I have bombs.
We can definitely make things happen here.
Unlucky.
Yes!
The list is rewarding us right now.
Up we go.
No, no!
No!
My smelter!
I better not find more trinkets.
That's all I'm saying.
Alright.
Eat those.
Hey!
Uh...
Yeah!
I'm gonna keep that.
I like it.
Oh my god.
That is a decent active.
Kill the big guy.
Big guy.
I mean, skulls are good, but...
Just a little bit unlucky not getting anything from them.
Come on, give me a black heart.
Black heart me.
You also gave me a lockdown pill.
Thank you.
I don't want it, but I appreciate the thought.
Okay, let's leave.
Destructive and disturbed, just like his father.
Look at who he has to look up to.
If you're drunk, you can get off you.
Shut up, Mac.
Shut up!
You just keep pushing me like this.
I'm leaving.
Good.
Leave.
We'll be fine without you.
Abandon us like you've abandoned yourself.
Guys, I think we're back.
Two of clubs?
Double bombs?
Yeah, actually.
I can probably just walk through here because I destroyed projectiles.
Wait, what?
These are...
Wait, who do I destroy?
Oh, someone back here.
Die!
It's not worth it.
Cartridge?
Oh, man.
The smelter.
He could have been smelting all day.
Okay, I mean, we're getting the...
The hearts back up.
Oh, there was a chest there.
Why you gotta do this to me now?
Suddenly, there's trinkets everywhere, you know?
When I throw away the smelter, it's just typical.
Make a black heart for me.
There's one more room back here.
And there's no key yet, by the way.
Very unlucky.
The emperor teleports a boss room.
I don't care about that.
Let's find the beam of light from the sky.
Oh, look at this big rock right here.
Oh, never mind.
I thought something cool may have happened.
Health up.
Okay.
Not mad about that.
He's pooping out a lot of pills for me.
Yeah, my damage is good, man.
No complaints there.
The build is solid.
Even these guys, they normally take a lot of shots, you know?
Bombs are...
Okay.
Well, we had 12 of each.
Still no key.
Isaac gets...
You know what?
Why not?
We're flip-flopping between big and small.
Just like me in real life.
The Hank man?
Nah.
Okay, the list!
The list!
We did it!
Finally.
Okay, we're missing one room back here.
Get out of there.
Wow, man!
Let's get small again.
Okay, well, nothing else we can do here.
Let's go to the lights.
You need to confess your sins and become saved.
Let his life inside you cleanse your soul.
You are insane.
You are taking us too far.
Did you hear how you sound?
Pray with me.
Pray for your salvation.
Come, pray.
It's a little risky for me to eat those mushrooms in case they blow up, right?
But, I mean...
Wait, did I take damage there?
Yeah, we're gonna blow him up from now on.
No more taking chances.
We got the chariots.
That's actually not bad.
Yeah, he died.
I'm gonna pick up the other card on the way back.
What's that?
Ah, man!
Uh...
Wait, how would that work with Smelter?
Would it just infinitely keep working?
I wonder.
I think I'll take that.
It's like a small insurance policy.
The Hierophant!
Love to see it.
That's one of the best cards I can make right now.
Grab that.
Gonna destroy this man.
Imagine Smelter, huh?
Should've kept it.
The Smelter play was the right one if I had only believed in it all the way, you know?
I shouldn't have pussied out.
Oh, there's a big room.
Lots of breakable stuff we can destroy here.
What's happening here?
Oh, you're down there.
I see.
There's someone up here.
Break it all.
Knowing how things usually go at this point in the game, and with how much HP I have, I would bet probably half my life savings that I'm gonna win.
Not that that's, like, a lot, but I would bet it anyway.
The amount of damage I have and all that, I mean...
And then this thing now.
Magician.
Oh, Magician!
Imagine, like, all three conjoined, all aiming towards the enemy.
That's insane, right?
Definitely using Magician.
Yeah, pick it up.
Make me a...
Oh, okay.
Blood donation.
No.
The tower.
That's the one with the bombs.
I wonder why it's called the tower.
What does a tower have to do with bombs?
The lovers.
Oh, yeah, definitely.
Eat him up.
I'm drowsy.
That's actually not bad, either.
Guys, this could actually be better than Magician.
If we eat this pill...
During the last boss...
I mean, come on.
I think it's gonna work.
That is actually massive.
Magician was good, but this is better.
It says it lasts for the room, but can I trust it?
Maybe it only lasts a little bit in the room, you know?
Sometimes they lie about that.
Don't destroy that one.
Still no key.
I don't know how that works.
Two soul hearts!
Baby, yeah!
Very good.
Wrong key.
Okay, now, lights.
Basement one.
Um, this way?
The Hierophant!
Yeah-ho-ho!
Don't do me, Bas!
We're full HP now.
This is exactly what we need.
Let me stop shooting him diagonally.
Uh...
Actually, yes.
We'd rather have bombs...
...compared to keys right now.
And being able to shoot down the projectiles with my own projectiles is pretty good.
Fruity plum has appeared.
What did I just do that unlocked that?
Like, did I reach some kind of milestone or something?
He wants coins.
Uh...
Yeah, I'm gonna give it to you.
You better poop out something good.
Yep, that's not bad.
Blackheart.
I'm actually gonna save it.
Just in case I lose some damage on this floor.
Or lose some HP.
The devil.
Troll bombs.
There we go.
Oh!
Balls of steel!
Oh, wait, that's...
That was useless.
Ah, whatever.
I will grab the...
The car generator again, though.
Now go this way.
Okay, there's the beam.
There may not be anything underneath these rocks...
...in this level.
Maybe I've just gotten unlucky.
It sure...
Oh my god.
Okay.
Good thing I saved that blackheart, huh?
Judgment.
Um, yeah, okay.
We can play this game again.
Bumbo!
I like it.
Let's get the heart.
Wow, another blackheart?
Can you watch keys?
I'm giving away everything I can right now.
Before the finish line.
Oh.
Man, what are these chests?
Come on.
Now I just need to find someone that takes bombs as well...
...and I will be golden.
Uh, wait.
Squeezy, doesn't that do more than that?
Let me look at my stats.
What?
Usually it gives, like, tears or something.
Huh.
That's weird.
Okay, let's get out.
Here we go.
I'm calling it now.
This is gonna be a fucking smackdown.
This is gonna be easy for me.
No, I don't have a...
Gah.
So yeah, I mean, we didn't find a key, so...
Rip.
Just unlucky.
I wanna...
Go in!
Mom's key.
That's not the right key, though.
Doubles the amount of pickups.
Okay, well...
Now I'm gonna go open the other chest, because we have this.
Back...
Wait, back launch?
Chances...
When taking damage to destroy the trinket and spawn the launch item.
Uh...
I think I like my current one more.
Again.
The smelter would have been killer to have.
I keep saying it.
Time to face the music.
We're gonna put on National Geographic.
In hopes that we're gonna get something useful...
To learn.
Cool information about the earth.
Instead, there's gonna be random people on an ice lake.
Driving around in monster trucks.
We're gonna hate our life.
Let's do this.
I'm gonna dog your mom.
That sounds really wrong.
Oh, come...
Dude, I was shooting the wrong target for the longest time.
Okay.
Come on then, bro.
I ran into it.
That was me.
Yeah.
Trigger it.
Trigger, trigger, trigger.
We got him.
It's time for the beast.
Wait, what?
Speed up pill?
Where's that pill?
I'm gonna make myself drowsy.
I'm drowsy.
Aye, aye, aye, aye.
He actually got me.
Even in slow motion.
That's embarrassing.
Actually, I should just stay out of his way.
I have diagonal shot.
This way, he can never hit me.
I think I should just go close and really hit him.
The question is, does drowsy last throughout all the stages?
We'll find out.
I think so.
Wait, what are you doing?
Kill him.
Good.
Next.
Look at all my flies.
Oh.
We can't...
Oh, wait.
Look at this little guy.
We got the emperor.
Wait, what is that one?
I'm afraid of clicking that.
I don't think I should click that.
Okay, he mad now.
Oh.
Man, he doesn't stand a chance.
Now we have this guy come in.
Come on now.
I don't have all day.
He's gonna do the scythes.
Aw, man.
I bombed myself.
I did it again.
Let's not try to be fancy.
Let's just kill him.
I'm trying to style on him.
It's not a good idea.
Okay, come on.
We are gonna bomb him, though, when he starts chasing us.
There we go.
Look at all those boogers.
Is he about to do...
Okay.
Are you gonna laser me?
Whoa!
Nice.
Look at this conjoined, man.
I'm hitting him so much.
Yeah!
It feels good, man.
It felt good.
That's what I needed.
I needed that.
I needed that so bad.
Wonderful.
Unfortunately, we didn't find the key.
We got unlucky.
So we couldn't unlock, well, whatever his name is.
Evil Isaac.
Messed up Isaac.
I don't even know what you want to call it.
Let me try another character.
What have we not done yet?
Let me see here.
What about Cain, actually?
Let's go home with Cain.
I like it.
I'm on cloud nine now.
Felt so good to get a win.
It's been 42 years.
I told you it was the start.
Okay, so Cain has two hearts.
So it's not a lot.
Okay, we have a half a heart there.
Alright, this room is going to be annoying.
I see a tinted...
Oopsie daisy.
Oh wait, I can just do drive-bys.
Good.
Not bad.
This is a solid strategy.
These guys are going to be a little hard.
Yeah.
How am I even going to do that?
Now we can go grab this half a heart.
We also got to get a buffered.
This time, angels.
Unless, of course, you know, things change.
And we have to take demons for whatever reason.
Oh my god.
Oh!
Jesus!
What the fuck do you do here?
Too little place.
Space.
Room.
I'm glad this wasn't the second floor.
We didn't lose any demon.
Okay, that's a buffer for next floor.
Coupon as well.
No money though.
I'm considering blowing up that machine.
To get some money.
I feel like hitting people from above is harder than the sides.
At least for me.
Like, when I'm above them on the screen, it's just, for some reason, harder to hit them.
It's less natural.
No.
Don't do this to me, man.
Why you gotta give me the worst item in the entire game?
Let me read this again.
Uh...
Okay.
Dude.
Okay, well, we're moving faster.
Could be a nice way to get out of dodge.
If something were to happen.
Other than that, useless.
Like, for example, if I'm here and I gotta go...
Yeah!
Right?
Pulse worm.
Okay.
Wait, I had this?
Locked chest can be opened without using a key.
No, I like this.
Are you kidding me?
When did I get that?
Oh, did I have it on me?
Maybe I did.
Ah!
Hey!
I did something.
God damn it!
Oh!
Oh my god!
I'm done!
I can't win.
Wait, we have one bomb.
That was a tented rock, right?
Oh, this is it.
Save me.
Yes!
That's what we needed.
Come on, man.
I'm gonna mess you up.
In fact, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna fucking...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna spin on you.
You like...
You like when I spin?
I like to spin.
Get spun on.
Hey!
Oh, no.
Okay, no more spinning!
We're done spinning.
I'm getting baited by the item.
It's a terrible item.
Get away from me.
Yep, good.
HP.
Please, I need HP up.
I need HP up.
Come on.
Give me breakfast.
Lunch.
Whatever.
Dinner.
Cat food.
Oh, not the booster pack.
One of the worst items in the entire game as well.
Yeah, that's a good card.
Justice.
Temperance.
I mean...
Hmm.
I mean, I could use Joker here.
No!
No, no, no!
Nope!
No.
We're not doing that because that locks us into...
Demons.
But I will bring the Joker...
With me.
Two of diamonds.
Uh...
Wait, wait.
Uh, 40 damage.
I'm gonna buy a heart.
Wait, I don't have enough.
I will have enough.
Shit!
Didn't mean to donate.
Yeah.
Uh...
Could also buy a pill.
Is it gonna be health up?
Oh, no.
Infinite regression.
Or whatever.
We don't like that.
Ah, well.
At least we got, uh...
One blue heart out of that.
Uh, yeah.
Move on.
We're gonna grab the Joker and save it.
We're not gonna use it yet.
Until we have...
Angels.
This is the plan.
See, 100% demon now.
So using the Joker here would actually be a mistake, right?
You wanna use it when you don't have a chance anyway.
Nah.
I can't believe he got a hit in on me like that.
Fuck it.
Get out of there.
I need to start focusing.
I can't be taking potshots like this.
Wait, can I hit back projectiles?
If they shoot at me and I spin?
Maybe.
That's a lot of poop.
I will save the poop.
Let's say I get an item that gives me the ability to get items from poops.
Uh, I don't like this room.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Spiders like this are gonna be the enemy.
This is, this is like...
It's impossible.
I don't know what to do.
I just don't know what to do.
I'm gonna spin on him.
Okay, we still got a buffer.
Get away from me.
Hoi.
Get spun on.
I gotta learn it, right?
No bombs, unfortunately.
Let's head this way.
We gotta spin!
When I'm in a corner, it's actually good.
I wish he would spin faster.
Don't pick that up yet.
That comes later.
We can take a peek.
Cheap card.
Starter deck.
Ooh.
Hold two cards at once.
All future pill drops are replaced with cards.
That is actually something I would consider.
The only thing is...
I don't have money.
The eternal problem.
In life.
Alright, he's kinda gonna jump from Africa?
Yep.
Wow.
Jump at me!
How?
He predicted my movement!
How did he know I was going to go that way?
I don't believe it.
What is that item?
It's a new one!
Montezuma's Revenge?
While firing tears charges a poop attack.
That fires from Isaac's rear when released.
The attack fires a beam for three seconds with limited range that deals rapid damage to enemies it touches.
Oh, I see.
So it's like, uh, diarrhea.
Let me see how this works.
Oh!
It even has little poop chunks in it!
That is exciting.
This is actually like a little...
Tiniest Azel?
But a shitty version, you know?
Does it destroy poops?
Oh, right.
Let's do it the other way.
I have to remember.
Oh!
It's from where I move!
Ah, okay.
It's not the direction I'm shooting.
It's how I'm moving.
Okay, that makes it weirder.
Maybe I don't like it then.
But it is exciting.
It's a cool new item.
I wish I had a bomb for this.
I'm gonna poop on this guy so hard.
Oh, especially when he changes me like this?
Wow!
Yeah, this thing slaps.
I wanna kind of line them up here.
That's incredible.
Synth oil.
Dude, extra two damage on that?
Phew.
That's a lot.
Um...
I think we just jumped down.
Yep.
We're going for angels.
Okay, so what is the...
We have darkness.
Ohoy!
Alright.
We got a front poop and a back poop now.
Oh my, come on.
Destroy these.
I love the little poop chunks that come out as well.
Guy's been eating fiber.
The sound makes it even better.
There's gotta be a lot of lasers and poop in this run.
Imagine I get brimstone next.
Then we have poop from the back, brim from the front, and a little brim from the vanguard.
Not bad, eh?
No, I missed.
Holy shit.
That was close.
It's definitely awkward to aim.
Nice.
You want bombs?
I don't have any, unfortunately.
I'm actually gonna go in here just to have a peek.
Okay.
I have 15 coins.
We can buy something.
33.8% angel.
Guys, this means we're gonna use joker.
No.
We're gonna do boss first, and if we don't get an angel, we use joker.
You ready?
There we go.
It's Chad.
I'm gonna poop on Chad.
But I'm not gonna read Chad.
Heh heh heh.
Get it?
Oh.
Okay, then.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Okay.
Careful, careful.
We didn't get angels, so what do we do?
We click the button.
That's wonderful!
Holy water for me.
We can't even destroy the guy.
Man.
Can't even destroy the flames.
It's fine, though.
I like holy water.
Holy water is kind of goaded.
In my opinion, at least.
I think it's good.
It's a good item.
Yeah, full health.
Opens that.
Actually, it's so nice that we got some bombs there.
Oh, wait, you're alive.
Little poop chunks are actually helping a bit.
I didn't hit anything there.
It's so hard to aim with it.
Imagine we get another Joker.
Nice.
We got Notch's axe.
Little Swedish person.
Weal the pickaxe.
Ooh.
I think I definitely want that instead of my spinny-weeny.
Or more like spinny-loosy.
I'll take it.
We can buy a pill or a key.
I'll take a pill.
Pheromones.
Yeah.
Pheromones are not exciting.
Oh, but look at this.
Uh.
Oh, wait.
I think I may have tried this once.
I don't think I can actually...
be far enough away where I don't take damage, you know?
But I may have to test that again.
Ooh.
Saving that.
No, wait.
Uh.
Yeah, we have one more room.
We gotta go do that first.
No taking chances here.
Liberty Cab.
No.
So watch.
I'm gonna stand here.
There's gotta be like a range where I don't take damage, right?
We will find the secrets.
Okay, so hold on.
Ooh.
Actually, we can go step.
Yo!
This is the standard setup for stepping.
We got a heart there, heart there, heart there.
We actually have hearts everywhere.
Time to step.
Oh.
I take a full heart of damage.
Well, in that case, I'm...
I'm gonna grab this.
And now, when I step, I should have half a heart, right?
Okay.
Go back and heal again.
In fact, let's take the, uh, the double heart.
See, I'm glad I didn't pick up the eternal heart yet.
Oh, you know what?
Before I do this, maybe I should go down here.
And actually clear out the last room.
Hey, I made a bridge like that!
Look!
Sick.
Oh, I wanna go in here.
Oi, oi, oi, oi.
That was kind of a bummer of a room, but...
It's fine.
Let's look for secrets.
Wait, this actually consumes a lot of battery.
Oh!
Oh-ho-ho-hey!
Check it out, man!
Uh-oh.
Oh!
I could not see where he was!
Like, there was so much crap on my screen!
I had so many stupid followers...
That looked exactly like this guy!
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Fuuuuck!
And now the win streak is gone.
Just like that!
Take me out in the shed and fuck me.
We had so much lined up as well.
Eternal Heart and all kinds of stuff.
Like...
Dude...
The weird thing is, I'm not even tilted.
I'm just used to it, you know?
Like, this is just how this game is.
It's not even, like, an extraordinary event.
It's just another day at the office.
It's to be expected.
Wait, we actually start with four damage?
That has to be, like, the highest damage...
Like, the base damage of any character.
God, I wish you could just die over there.
You are so annoying.
There we go.
I think this room just gave me an ulcer.
Yeah, I can feel it.
There's a lump in my leg.
Oh, not this again.
Don't do this to me.
Okay, we gotta kill the spiders first, obviously.
But...
They're fleeing, right?
Got them.
Okay.
Three coins.
No money.
I mean, three keys.
Not really intrigued by anything in there.
More ki- What about bombs?
Can I please have some bombs?
Is that too much to ask?
I've got multiple uses of bombs so far.
Uh-oh.
Woo!
Maybe this will give me some bombs.
Wait, that just opened...
That's weird.
Good.
Very good.
Wow.
Here we go.
A re-roll.
Oh, Taurus is the one...
Huh.
Hmm.
I-I don't...
I don't like it, man.
I really don't.
I'd rather just get a bomb and a key and try and re-roll.
Or maybe just one bomb so I can destroy it and re-roll that way.
Wait, really?
No bombs at all?
Bruh.
No way.
There's also a tinted rock I can't get now.
This is pain.
This is pure pain.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna pick up the item because it's actually just that bad.
I don't like it.
Like, minus 0.35 speed is horrible.
Right?
Always be on the move against this dude.
It's one of the hardest bosses.
Just because he moves and jumps so fast.
Oh, I don't like these nests.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Thank God.
Heal, heal.
Oh.
That has to be the hardest first boss you can have.
Ooh.
Now that is great.
And we get healed.
Lovely.
Still no bomb, though.
Which sucks.
Yeah.
Not grabbing Taurus.
Oh.
That is the weirdest room I've ever seen.
What was the point of that little display?
Wait.
So we have a debuff right now.
Oh, we can't see our hearts.
Right.
Okay.
That's what that is.
How?
I thought this was like an angel item.
How is that in here?
This is a really good item.
I'm glad.
Dude.
The pills are so good today.
At least on this one.
We've had some bad pills earlier, but so far, so good.
The haunt.
Well, we can't take damage, actually.
I could have been at an angel party!
And what is that smell?
Nice!
We like the midnight snack.
Come on.
The midnight snack is the best snack.
Things always taste better at midnight.
Meow, meow.
We don't have a stepper, but we do have a cursor.
I'm ready.
Tower.
Chariot.
Uh, chariot.
I mean, I can use that to get out of here, but that's kind of a waste.
Especially because I can heal back here.
Yep.
I got one coin.
I don't think we should go in there.
And one bomb.
Man, bombs are really scarce.
For some reason.
I still don't understand this freaking...
door, man.
Hold on.
Let me see here.
What did I write down about this?
Fight room.
Opens when...
Ah, but hold on.
There's two different fight rooms, right?
There's a small fight room.
There's a fight room.
And there's a fight room.
Right?
There's the difference.
Uh, so this one's definite.
We can actually remove this.
All you need is full red hearts.
This one, though...
I don't know.
Not sure.
I think we should leave.
Although, I see a potential for a secret room right here.
Let me just double check all the walls.
This is it.
It has to be.
I said it.
Oh, ho, ho.
Okay.
It wasn't really that worth.
I mean, it was worth.
But it wasn't that worth.
You know?
Wait, do I have some kind of...
AOE attack?
How am I dealing damage to two of these poops at the same time when I shoot?
That's weird.
I can't believe that mine is 99.
But hey, maybe it doesn't matter because we weren't going to go in anyway, right?
Actually, yes.
Wait, now we have 100% demon.
So wait, angels can only appear on the fourth floor.
Or what?
Is that the trick here?
Oi!
Look at that!
That's a great item to just find like that.
Oh, oh, oh, okay.
Hoish!
Wow!
Holy buffer!
Best fight room ever?
That's got to be one of the best fight rooms of all time, right?
Another one!
Guys, I'm calling it now.
We can't lose this run.
It's easy from now on.
Notice how I didn't call that last run.
Watch this be a good pill as well.
Friends till the end.
I mean, it's a good pill.
It's not that great, but it's a good pill.
We've had a perfect track record so far.
Nice.
Let's not grab that.
Actually, we cannot even grab it, so.
Oh, god.
Oh!
Oh, man!
Matrix!
I'm Neo.
Yep.
I want you to peer next to me.
There we go.
That was good?
That was no spoon.
Wait, where's my holy water?
Oh, what the?
Step into my office.
Do I?
Oh!
Wow!
I know kung fu.
I have a sentence?
Meow!
Party time!
That was satisfying.
A safety cap.
Yeah, okay.
Better than the bombs, I guess.
We have four already.
Wait, okay.
I need to calculate this.
No, no.
Oh, wait.
Stay here instead.
Shit.
That was not a good time.
That was not a good time either.
That's a good time.
It's not a good time.
Like, this room is nuts.
Wait, how did I do this room in the past?
I'm so gonna...
Wait, how?
Go!
Like, Neo can't even dodge inanimate objects, you know?
Agent Smith all day, no problem.
But a fucking stone?
Just sitting there going...
Hoop!
Nope.
Too much!
Can't stand the hoop.
Oh, tempting me with the demon.
I reject the demon.
I do indeed reject.
I'm going angel.
Wait, I just realized how I'm gonna do this.
You literally just walk in.
There's a delay.
Ah.
That's it.
I figured it out.
It's actually easy.
I'm embarrassed.
But if you don't walk in and utilize it in the beginning, impossible.
Nobody can actually do it.
Did you see the precision?
Wasn't that immaculate?
Look at this!
Huh!
I have a sentence.
I know Gonkata.
Libra.
Stat upgrades are balanced.
Okay.
Lost some speed.
Lost some tears.
Gained some...
Okay.
I mean...
Yeah.
Decent, I would say.
Not great.
Not terrible either.
I don't really want anything in here at all.
Uh.
Blue map is actually kinda goaded.
But we can't get the money for it.
The map is already explored.
I think I'm gonna gamble with the pill.
Hey!
There it is, baby!
Oh yeah.
Oh wait.
Everything is balanced from now on.
Right.
That's how that works.
So it's not just that one time.
It's from now on and forever.
Do I like it then?
Still don't have an active item.
Uh.
Let's go out.
No!
I have a little tinkle in my nether region telling me that there's something great in here.
Watch.
Okay, never mind.
I will never again listen to that tingle.
That's over.
Okay.
Our luck had to run out at some point.
Oh, I thought I could at least eat these.
It's too bad.
Do I want this?
Actually...
No, no, no.
Keep this.
Let's get the hell out of here.
How did I get ten bombs?
Rup!
Yeah, look!
That's the trick.
We gotta figure it out.
And it's beautiful.
Now is the age of the angel.
Angels shall rule the earth.
And I've gotten in their good graces.
Why didn't he get stunned when he walked into my office?
That's what I want to know.
No, don't go in there yet.
Oh!
And boink!
Oh, I was gonna give you some water.
Body of Christ.
Did you know...
That...
The Hossite Wars were a thing.
Jan Hoss.
I don't know why I know that.
I saw a documentary about it recently.
And the reason I say that is because they were actually rebelling against the church.
Or the idea behind only giving wine to the people and not bread.
No, only giving bread to the people and not wine.
At the church communion.
They wanted to get drunk.
That's my theory.
I don't think they gave a shit about actually honoring the old traditions.
They wanted to get drunk.
Just like all the rich people and all the nobles.
They love that stuff.
Now you know.
Never forget it, okay?
It'll be on the test.
Mom's razor!
I don't like it.
Actually, I do like it.
And we're gonna blow this up.
Come on.
I need a health uphill.
I haven't had one of those in 10 years.
Ah!
Okay, I'll take it!
Shot speed up.
Ah, but hold on a minute.
That one didn't get distributed.
So that one was not balanced.
What's up with that?
Liars!
They're lying to me again.
I can't believe I got hit by that!
That's a boomerang.
I could buy a card.
Why not?
I don't like my wheel of fortune anyway.
The sun!
How do I do it?
How does he do it?
You can't explain it.
It is unexplainable.
I could use it here and actually gain understanding of the secrets of this realm.
But...
Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
Secrets discovered.
Actually, it only reveals one of the secret rooms.
That is like...
Not Pog, you know?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I have a real-life friend who says Pog in real life, you know?
And it's...
Makes me feel a weird way.
I don't even know how to respond to it.
I'm just like, yeah, okay.
It makes me laugh, though.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
What does Pog even mean?
Like, it's an acronym, right?
Means, uh...
Please...
Ovaries...
Gratitude.
Or a pleasant ovary gratitude.
I don't know.
It has to mean something about ovaries.
It's the only thing that makes sense.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh, I'm thinking about the Hossite Wars.
Bombs are key.
Do I want that?
Actually, yes.
Dude, I haven't had a single, like, bad pill in this entire run, if I'm not mistaken.
Actually, we had one.
But almost perfect track record.
Okay, now we want to go...
here.
This guy's a bomber.
No!
I ran into the...
Ah!
Focus, you idiot!
Dude, that was so close!
Oh!
I nearly panicked there!
We have 36% angel.
We can't waste this.
Oh, no.
Can I hit both of these?
Please.
It may actually be possible.
Brother!
We're cooking!
And now we do the boss without getting hit.
No getting hit time.
No hit.
Go!
Okay, this is...
This boss is actually okay.
The problem is, he's floating.
Ha ha ha!
I fucking hate myself!
Ah!
I've never truly felt like a boy or a girl!
Guzzy Capri!
Oh my...
I just want to sink into my chair.
I hate it.
Like, I...
That...
Okay, guys, you know what?
I probably wouldn't have gotten the angel anyway.
It was 36% chance, you know?
And if there's one thing everyone knows, is that if there's a 36% chance of getting a shot, you're not gonna get it, you know what I mean?
Even 50% is not good.
You want at least 100.
It's the truth.
Um...
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Getting a little Stephen Familia...
But that's not good.
That's a trinket, right?
Yeah, I don't wanna be at half a red heart.
Are you crazy?
I'm actually gonna go...
Curse myself.
Now, check this out.
Oh, man, really?
Aha!
Health up!
Come on, come on.
Come on, baby.
Ah!
Okay, we got a bad pill.
Finally, the run...
was broken.
Or the combo was broken.
Actually, there's a heart back here I can take.
I have so many bombs!
I, uh...
I feel like I should be looking for more secrets.
Don't even have an active.
Okay, I have a feeling.
Right here.
Oh, imagine.
Imagine, though.
Not in this room, because it's, like, elongated and weird.
Can I hit two at the same time?
Oh!
Unfortunately, didn't get anything.
Imagine if we got another mushroom.
Okay, I shouldn't waste all my bombs.
Maybe I'll waste a couple more bombs.
This one.
Right there.
Okay, this one.
This one.
Oh, no, it can't be.
Maybe here?
Okay, no more!
I'm done!
No more bombing!
I am done.
I will definitely exchange this for a heart.
Hey, wait!
I forgot about this room.
Hold on a minute now.
Eight...
Uh, eight...
Nine coins now?
In total.
How good am I?
Ten coins!
We'll save it.
Yep.
That's actually not that bad.
Not too bad.
You guys know about Gussie Capri, though, right?
It's the only person in the United States who has...
Uh...
An Android.
Like a Google Pixel.
It's quite remarkable.
We're gonna be dodging all this.
Also, what's up with the lack of tinted rocks here?
I have been looking.
And there wasn't anything.
Ooh, I wanna destroy some of these skulls.
Let's save our...
Oh, wait.
Did I just lose a bunch of...
Angel?
Oh.
Oh, no.
Well...
Guys, I...
I'm gonna say it.
Okay?
I think I've come to a conclusion.
Angels suck.
And here's why.
There's almost no angel rooms.
And you gotta play almost perfect to get them.
And when you do get them, you get some crap anyway.
Demons are superior.
Like, by far.
Ooh, I like that one.
Joy, they're coming fast.
Good thing they went into my office there.
Well, the buffer's not gonna matter anymore.
We already fucked that up, so...
Don't care about the blue heart.
Nope.
Hey!
Nice!
We love that.
Hey!
Dude, what's happening right now?
Fucking pills, man!
I'm tempted to buy this for another pill.
Watch.
I mean, okay.
That's not bad.
Not too bad.
Let's keep exploring.
In fact, since we don't have a buffer now anyway, I feel free.
I can go into curse rooms.
I can do all kinds of things.
Without feeling bad, you know?
Oh, god.
Nice.
Office tactics.
Hup, bup, bup, bup, bup.
Oh!
Woohoo!
How?
I feel like that was more luck than anything else.
I let Jesus take the wheel on that one.
I admit it.
I had a feeling!
How do I do it?
How?
I just can't explain it, you know?
Wait, this guy is really annoying.
Oh, there we go.
Aha!
Definitely doing this.
Don't mind if I do?
Step into my office.
Pay to win.
Uh...
Yo!
That's amazing.
What is happening with these pills?
Oh, I picked up the wrong heart.
I should have taken the half heart.
Okay, no matter what happens in this run, guys, I cannot complain about not getting lucky.
Like, I've had my fair share of luck.
Now it's all up to me to take it the rest of the way.
The game did all it could to support me.
Now I just gotta, you know, grasp the hand that has been extended towards me.
And smile.
Got him.
Uh...
I got four bombs.
I could maybe destroy some stuff here.
Didn't work out that time.
My office welcomes you.
Would you like some coffee?
Can I offer you some water, maybe?
Oh my...
What a shot.
I will give you that.
I mean, there was 18% chance of it happening.
It didn't happen, but there was a chance.
I'm not done exploring.
Oh, careful.
There's a couple places I haven't been.
Oi, oi, oi.
I hate the jumping jacks.
Like, he kept...
Look at that!
Unfair.
Crazy.
I'm in some sort of trance right now.
It's like I'm not even looking at my character.
I'm just looking at my projectiles and I'm moving.
Damn!
Wait, something's wrong?
Spawns a puddle of slowing black creep.
Eh.
I can keep it.
I mean...
This is insane.
We actually have a shop, but I forgot what was in there.
Honestly, at this point, as soon as I get a health up pill, I'm actually just gonna ignore all pills.
Because chances of getting a bad pill increases the more I take good pills.
You know what I mean?
Because the good pills I'll recognize.
I know what they are now.
I can buy this.
And that.
Uh-oh.
Not too bad.
Do want to go into that curse room.
I have a feeling there's something incredible in there.
It's a tingle.
Take notes, kids.
Learn from the master.
Oh.
Nice.
And this way.
Yep.
We're done, right?
Wait, I forgot about the credit card.
That's why I went back to the shop.
You know what?
I'll save it for the next shop.
The next shop is bound to have even better items.
You'll see.
100% angel.
The name of the game now is to find the boss room and not enter it just yet because we need a teleport card.
Okay.
Money.
I'm playing pretty well right now.
Oh, no.
Yeah, they're doing the jumping.
I expect to take at least two hearts of damage here.
Wow.
Not sure what I got hit by.
Wait, power pill.
That's the one that makes me...
Ooh.
Let's save that for a boss.
Or even here.
Wait, what?
Are they running from me?
It felt like they were avoiding me on purpose.
It's the fool again.
It...
Okay.
It's consistent.
So, if there's an X on a skull, it's gonna drop the fool.
That's what that is?
Isn't that weird?
Let me write that down, actually.
Okay.
I feel like that's super random.
Special.
Uh, X on skull.
Uh...
Pill.
Don't take it yet.
We're gonna leave it for later.
Step into my office!
Doors always open.
Get up.
I don't think he can get stunned by that.
Okay, he's dead.
Good.
Never mind.
He got stunned by it.
Oh, hold on a second.
This is a double whammy.
Double trouble!
Uh...
Wait, why did I even go in here?
I'm a maniac.
Oh, wait.
This is not a double whammy.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I'm so confused.
Why did I go this way?
I don't even know what I'm talking about right now.
I'm so confused.
What did I mean by double whammy?
I don't know what's happening right now.
Guys, I feel like...
I feel like the fever is creeping, you know?
It's there.
Lurking.
And the dark matter of my brain.
Okay!
Now give me a shop!
I've got a credit card!
Step into my office.
Take off your shoes.
That would be weird, wouldn't it?
Like, if you have someone step into your office and you go, can you take off your shoes?
You don't do that.
Leech!
Okay, let me think.
No.
We're gonna re-roll until we get the best of the best.
Ah, but hold on.
Mid-charge.
I'm not charging shit.
Oh, wait.
I am charging shit if I pick this up, though.
Then I will be charging.
Ah!
That one, though.
Yike!
Dankeschön!
That's a good one.
I actually feel free as well because I don't have the list anymore.
Oh, that's a friend.
Okay.
This is the best mom's bottle of pills of all time.
Damn.
Okay.
You ready?
What do I want?
I mean, everything.
A power pill!
And we even have this.
What's this?
Wheel of Fortune.
Yeah.
I mean, I feel like I should donate.
Allows active items to store up to two charges.
Okay.
Ah, too bad.
Oh, I should have taken...
Didn't I have some extra battery?
No.
No, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna save my money?
No, this is the mom level.
So I should not save my money.
Yeah, just...
Just...
Yeah, fill it up.
Oh, man.
Oh!
Okay.
I'm gonna donate.
The rest goes in here.
There we go.
Power pill.
Yes, sir.
I'm happy.
I feel good.
I could power pill in there, actually.
But I'm saving that for mom!
Oh, god damn.
Wait, we actually have a 100% angel?
Our payday is coming!
These guys avoid my offices anyway.
Oh, oh, oh!
Okay.
I'm actually gonna use the pill here, I think.
Am I?
I have bombs!
Check it out.
This is what we're gonna do.
Almost.
Yes!
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
I'm a kiss.
Yes!
Now we go say hi to mom.
Ah, buh, buh, buh, buh, buh!
Before we do.
We grab the card.
Oh, then I should have used the pill here, I guess.
Ah, whatever.
We got the card.
Mom!
My ear's itchy.
Boy!
That was so close.
Yeah, yeah.
Did I just get hit twice there, like a dumbass?
What's wrong with me?
Wait, I'm not dealing any damage to mom here.
There we go.
That's a good office.
How did I get hit?
She got me good with that.
Oh, my God.
There we go.
Angel time!
Monstrons.
Large golden aura that deals damage.
I actually kind of like this one.
It's okay.
I do like it.
Nice.
Now.
Go.
Wait, do we need to do something before we leave?
What about Fight Club?
Was that closed?
It was.
Ah, bah, bah, bah!
Oh.
Now I leave.
Okay, now we gotta see whether or not we can get lucky with the key.
Ah, after this one, of course.
Damn!
Shit, man!
Another power pill.
You know what?
No, I'm not gonna use it.
Not yet.
Can I possibly get in there?
No.
I haven't had flying in a while.
Jesus!
Hourglass is pretty good.
Yeah, maybe I'll save for that.
But it's also kind of late to get it, you know what I mean?
Like, all the potential use cases have been, you know, what I mean to say is, it's not useful anymore.
The virus.
Yeah.
Wait, hold on.
Pill, pill, or not pill.
Ow.
For some reason, I thought we were at 3 out of 3 on spawn.
I must be thinking about some other character I played today.
Wait, did I actually get some kind of item that makes all pills good or something?
Not that one.
I don't know.
Lucky.
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God.
The teleport really messed with me.
Oh, wow.
I don't know how I did that without taking damage.
What now?
Here.
Dude, part of me wants to just go directly to boss.
Let's do it.
I could lose too much HP here.
I'm doing it.
Fuck it.
I spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
Oi, oi.
How did you have spent our savings?
I did that so well.
Something's wrong.
I like power pill more.
Yeah, they're running from me.
I definitely should be destroying these.
Oh, come on.
Really?
Okay, power pill would have been better in here.
Fuck!
That could have gone much worse.
Telepathy for dummies.
Fire mind?
Tears apply burning effect that damages enemies over time.
Chance for tears to explode on hit.
Wow.
Blood of the martyr.
Ooh.
That's just all around good.
This one was telepathy.
That is pretty good for beasts.
Because it's for the entire room.
Right?
Tears apply burning.
Oh, man.
I don't know.
I mean, these are all kind of good.
I could also reroll, actually.
They have 15 coins.
I'm gonna reroll.
Nod leaf?
No, thanks.
Speedball?
Okay.
Little...
Oh, man.
I feel like...
I kind of want this, but I'm also...
kind of wanting to reload again.
Halo.
Friendly ball.
Isn't that a Pokemon?
Throw again to release the captured enemy.
No, I don't want...
I don't want that.
Flush?
Ew.
No.
Host has.
Which may...
Makes Isaac immune to explosion damage.
Chance to block enemy shots and fire three bullets back.
Ooh, that's pretty good.
Leo.
Isaac can break...
I don't care about that.
Mutant spider.
Fires four tiers at once in an arc pattern.
Hmm.
But I lose a lot of stats.
I mean, it is pretty good.
It's basically like conjoined, but even better, you know?
Is that worth it?
I'm gonna do it.
It's basically a better conjoined.
Ho-ho!
Yeah.
Can I keep doing it?
There's a pedestal.
Oh.
Fuck you, then.
I like it.
Oh, yeah.
This is so good.
It's like an insane item, actually, if you think about it.
Black heart!
We needed that.
In fact, we need a couple more of those.
Okay, good to get some healing.
Also, we gotta look for the key.
Any tinted?
Get the green guy!
Not to be confused with Get the Gringo.
It's a great movie with Mel Gibson.
Actually, I haven't seen that in a while.
I wouldn't say great.
It's okay, you know?
Not a bad movie.
Friends till the end.
I think I should be doing this.
Yep.
Not bad.
Any more?
Kind of want to get a coins or bombs, or whatever it's called.
Keys or bombs.
Wait, what?
Okay.
Not sure what that's about.
Dude, this is such a huge increase to deep...
Oh my god, tapeworm?
Yeah, I guess I don't need to pay to win anymore.
I'm doing a lot of damage now.
Definitely destroying these.
One bomb left.
Transforms all pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies into bombs.
Well, there we go.
That's our way back to having bombs again.
Let me see exactly what it said.
Pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies.
Okay.
So we need to get a room with a lot of enemies.
I mean, what's wrong with being drunk?
We'll be fine without you.
Abandon us like you've abandoned yourself.
Sounds like he needed a drink to be near you.
You psycho.
Oy, oy.
Hey, one more puberty and we get to level up.
Bastard!
Took my black heart.
Enjoy my office.
It's a corner office.
Actually, it's not.
It's a center office.
Why would I lie about that?
Imagine lying about your office.
Damn.
Office!
Yeah.
We're done here.
Oh, God.
No.
I'm coming back.
Ace of clubs!
Fucking reaction times of a master god.
How good was that, huh?
Now we got bombs for Zeus.
Uh, ooh.
I want that.
Yoink!
A power pill!
Not bad.
I'll exchange some keys for bombs.
Why not?
Thank you.
No inanimate objects are the bane of my existence!
Fucking Ralph Finney.
Let's not forget Eternal!
Like, I...
My damage is not that great.
It's still kind of bad.
I need more damage.
Now we go.
Also, we have the guppy, uh, extra life thing.
That could, uh...
Save us.
Let his light inside you cleanse your soul!
You are insane.
You are taking this too far.
Did you hear how you sound?
Pray with me.
Pray for your salvation.
Oh, oh, oh!
Pray with us, I...
Fungi!
What does it do?
Makes me shoot faster, or...
I become big guy?
Not sure.
Huh.
I can't fly, unfortunately.
I was hoping to fly.
It's okay, though.
I can use my money in here?
Why not?
Give me an HP up item, or something.
Haha!
Thank you!
You know, if I was smart, I wouldn't have picked that up until after this floor.
In case I took more damage.
Because it heals me at the same time, right?
I've learned my lesson.
What is it with...
Okay, there's something going on with the bills.
I just refuse to believe I'm that lucky.
There is some kind of game mechanic that is happening that I don't understand.
But it's making all the pills good.
Or at least not bad.
See, I mean, that's not a bad pill, you know?
It's okay.
We're done here.
Oh, this could be nice.
Oh my god!
Okay, that's not good.
That's not good either.
Wait, what?
What is happening here?
Grants a large fire rate increase when collected coins, bombs, and keys are all...
We're actually close to that being the case?
Reveals the map and drops a card rune of soul heart.
Hey!
Okay.
We can probably do this.
If I use a couple keys...
I'm gonna take this.
I'm gonna try and make this work.
Two of hearts.
I don't need that.
Oh my god.
Louse!
No.
See, now the problem is I have too much money.
Oh god.
What makes you larger?
No thanks.
Unless...
Hold on, hold on, hold on a minute.
If I could become larger, do my projectiles get larger too?
Because look at them.
They're kind of massive.
Wait, I gotta test this.
Let me see.
If I stand here and I shoot left...
Okay, they're about that size.
Uh...
I can't tell.
I don't think so.
Oh wait, am I?
Oh, I can walk over things now.
Is that what fun guy does?
I get it.
Flat penny?
Dude, I have 24?
24?
I need to spend some money now.
Don't we still have the thing?
Oh no, it blew up.
But is there like a beggar?
Hold on.
Let's go back in a second here.
I just want to keep exploring.
Wiggle worm?
No.
Damn, this dude is tanky.
Wait, uh...
I should not pick this up.
Equality.
No.
Ah, damn.
I can't spend my money here.
I will...
We'll find a way...
To spend money.
Gotta be something.
Yeah, let's leave.
Man, the AoE damage is really good, though.
Ah!
Whoops.
Wait, Demon's Tail.
No, I don't want that.
I want equality.
Hey!
Very nice.
Here we go!
Oh, wait.
I used the bomb, but that's okay.
That's okay.
Wait, I don't...
Oh, hold on.
I can't blow him up.
Wait, I can walk through it, of course.
I need one more bomb.
Give me that.
Let's see how much increase I get.
It's not even that much more.
Am I crazy?
Wait, I don't think I want this rotten meat.
Is that a massive fire rate increase?
I feel like I got better stats from the other trinket I had.
Am I crazy?
Hold on.
Do I still have that?
Oh!
This thing's still...
Yay!
I'm back!
Time to re-roll, baby!
Mongo baby!
Uh, no.
No.
Actually.
Random effect of...
This could be good, actually.
Because I have such a high rate of fire.
I actually think this is a good item for me.
This will be good, I think.
Watch me.
And because we don't have equality anymore, I'm just gonna pick this up.
Yeah, fuck equality.
Oi, oi, oi.
Yeah, look at all these random effects here.
Another power pill!
I'm not gonna walk over everything.
What's that?
Oh.
Ayy, he wants keys?
I gotcha.
I gotcha, buddy.
What is that?
Fruity Plum.
It's a bouncy friend.
Wandering Familiar that deals contact damage, and propels itself around with small tiers that also damage enemies.
Okay.
Cool.
My job.
Oh!
No, I'm good, I'm good.
I thought I forgot something.
Let's see what we get.
Black heart!
I take that.
Unfortunately, we did not find a key again.
RNG is not on our side.
Feels bad, man.
Mom's pad.
Ooh!
Ah, it's gonna make three out of three, but it's shit.
Wait, is it actually?
No, I want, I want pills.
Pills are good.
Bring it on.
Dude, I look ugly as hell.
Look at my character.
Look at those two teeth.
And the pirate eye thingy.
Yikes.
We've seen some shit.
Okay, this time, attack the TV, you dummy.
Oh, God.
Okay, you know what?
Damage is pretty good, actually.
There we go.
Insane place.
Dude, will you stop already?
He just, he stepped into my office briefly there.
I don't think he liked it.
Here we go.
It's gonna be easy, man.
Are you kidding me?
I actually have surprisingly decent damage here.
I thought it would be worse.
Wait, what the hell was that?
Okay, we're losing some HP here.
What did I get hit by?
Let me get on the other side here.
Oh, he angry now.
Okay.
I went into the lava.
It was not good.
Hey, what's happening with my holy water?
It's bugging out.
So far, so good.
He's doing that stuff now.
No problem.
Next.
It's Beast.
Maybe we should let him stay within our aura.
Nah, that's too risky.
Not looking too great here.
Oh my god, my hitbox is too big.
I'm too fat.
We gotta destroy these.
I've still got it.
A pound of flesh has appeared.
Wonderful.
Very good.
Ah, too bad we didn't get the key, huh?
Man, we could have had...
Let me see.
Cain, cane, cane.
This one.
In fact, I got so unlucky today, twice in a row I didn't get the key.
That feels bad, man.
But it was still good.
I'm glad that we didn't just lose all day.
We actually had good runs.
That brings happiness to my smile.
And my face.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
What's up, guys?
Hey, the win streak is one now.
Next time, it'll be two.
And after that, three.
I can count.
You love that stream?
I loved it too.
It was great.
You know what it is?
It's the power of Friday.
The power of Friday can do things to you.
It's just a general feel, you know?
You're at the supermarket, and when you check out your wares, the cashier is like, have a good weekend, you know?
Like, you only hear that on Fridays!
And it boosts you up, man.
It pulls you up by the bootstraps, and it puts a smile on your face.
Everything you do on that day feels so much better.
Everyone is getting off work a little earlier.
Most people, at least.
You know, they're hanging out, doing things.
People are partying.
Yes.
It is the best day.
Confirmed.
You start your four-week vacation today.
Oh, is it summer vacation time?
Are a lot of you going on vacation now?
That's awesome, man.
That's a month.
Because I know my days in a month.
Very nice.
How many of you are students?
If you're a student, you must have, like, a long vacation now, right?
What are you guys studying?
I'm actually curious.
Any doctors?
Any medical doctors or something?
Lawyers?
Psychology, computer science.
I'm a corporate slave.
Quantitative finance student.
Okay.
Social media guy here.
What is a NEET?
Informatics?
What is informatics?
Wait, what is computer science even like these days?
Do they still adhere to the old ways of teaching?
Or have they sort of embraced all the AI stuff?
Is it part of the curriculum now?
Like, how does that work?
They can't just ignore it, right?
It's got to be included somehow.
NEET is someone who's not studying or working.
Oh, okay.
Environmental engineering here.
You know what?
I actually would love to do something like that.
Or something with environment, you know?
If I wasn't streaming, I would love to do something with renewable energies or something.
Because I think it's really cool.
Like, for example, I don't know why this is so fascinating to me.
But there's a company in Copenhagen called Copenhagen Atomics.
And they're trying to make the world's first, like, commercial molten salt reactor.
And I don't even know shit about it.
But I think it's fascinating.
I've been watching their lectures and stuff.
All their ads on YouTube.
Like, for some reason, I'm infatuated with this random ass company.
Doing this stuff.
Yeah, you can think of it as a...
Well, not fusion.
I don't know what you would call it.
Molten salt reactor.
Yeah.
I talked to someone...
Hold on.
Who went to my college and they said that CS students have an anti-AI culture.
And he looked at me funny for asking.
Oh.
Really?
I bet all of those people who are anti-AI in CS secretly use AI.
When they're not talking about it.
It's just too damn useful.
Like, agentic coding now has far surpassed my skills at coding.
I can't even keep up.
It is, like, ten times better at me than coding.
Not that I was very good to begin with.
But, you know.
At least for me.
What languages do I know?
I know Danish, German...
Well, my German is getting very rusty, but...
German and English.
Three languages.
Maybe greed mode next time.
Yeah, you're right, actually.
Next time, I promise we're gonna do greed and challenge.
Just to switch it up.
That way I can also keep my streak of one, you know?
It looks nice just sitting there at one.
Actually, one is so sad.
It has to be at least two, right?
Otherwise, it's not a streak.
That's just sad.
I hear from Maya University that they're reworking the curriculum to accommodate AI in the current industry.
But to my mind, I think it will become outdated soon.
I mean, AI is not going anywhere.
It is already so incredibly useful.
I'm talking about coding here.
Programming, coding...
Stuff like that.
It is absolutely not going to go away.
The only choice is to embrace it or incorporate it in some capacity.
Your German is beautiful, not gonna lie.
It was once.
But I'm at that stage where I can understand everything perfectly.
If a German is speaking to me in their native language and they're just going fast and using slang...
No problem.
I understand everything.
But when I speak it myself, I'm having such a...
Lot of trouble just getting the words.
You know?
I don't have the vocabulary anymore.
I totally forgot most of it.
I know what I want to say, but I just can't.
Nice music, right?
It's from Ark Raiders.
It has such incredible music, that game.
It's wild.
Do you understand dialects?
You mean in German?
I do.
I even understand the Glasgow people now.
Or Limmy, in other words.
I've watched so much of Limmy, I can understand it.
At first, I had no idea what that guy was saying.
You know?
His accent was so thick.
But now I get it.
I've just heard it so much.
Did you see Zario beating the Ender Dragon?
I did actually see it.
I've been following his journey.
I even saw his video where he was reacting to the speedruns.
And I had this weird...
What do you call it?
Memory of me doing the exact same thing, right?
Like, I also beat the Ender Dragon.
And then, not too long after...
I was watching those videos.
It's just funny to see.
I'm having trouble with other Scandinavian languages.
Like, Swedish or Norwegian.
I don't understand how people in Denmark understand those people.
Like, I don't get it.
For me, it's hard to understand.
If it's written, I can get it.
But spoken?
No.
No way.
He watched your vid when you discovered Enchanting?
He did?
Really?
Oh my god.
No way.
That makes me kind of starstruck.
Dude, Zario is someone I've been following for so long.
Because he's, like, mainly a World of Warcraft streamer.
And I've been playing so much World of Warcraft.
He's so good at the game, by the way.
Multiple rank ones, by the way.
I know he likes to bring it up.
Yeah.
I remember him reaching rank one, okay?
Scandies understand each other, but Danes are the exception, apparently.
Well, it's mostly that it's the young generation that don't understand the other Scandinavian countries.
Like, my grandma or, you know, all the old people in this country.
They all perfectly understand all the Swedish people and all the Norwegian people.
It's weird.
I guess it's because of their generation.
They had, like, TV channels they were watching.
Where half of it was Swedish or whatever.
And that's how they learned it, I imagine.
I don't know.
But yeah, all the young people...
You would be...
Having trouble finding someone who could understand it all.
If you get bored of the game, will you do a spoiler stream?
You're talking about Binding of Isaac.
I don't think so.
I've said this before, but I think this game is a game I could see myself playing for a long time.
Not like a main game.
Just, you know, with a lower cadence.
And I would return to it once in a while and work on my achievements and try to get further and further.
It'll be like a long project, you know?
Maybe even at the point in the future where it's gonna be one stream a month.
Something like that.
That's like 700 hours to get full achievements.
Well, you know.
I'm 35... 34?
I think I'm 34...
Am I 35?
I'm 34 years old, okay?
And I still have like 40 years in me.
We'll make it happen.
Wait, am I 30...
I was born in 92.
How old am I, guys?
I don't remember.
Literally.
I'm always confused.
Yeah, I'm 34.
Thank you.
Good.
February is my birthday.
My favorite character is...
Esasel.
OG Esasel.
I gotta say it.
It is.
If it wasn't for, you know, the fact that I'm not gonna unlock anything else with him...
Well, there's still things I haven't done with Esasel, but...
I'll be playing him all the time.
I would be trying to master that character, you know, to its fullest.
I have not played him in a while, you're right.
But that's because I wanna unlock more stuff, you know, and get the achievements and stuff.
Because that unlocks new items.
What about Esasel?
He's also cool.
A little more difficult to play, but fun.
I should play more Esasel.
Maybe I'll play...
Esasel next time in one of the Greed runs.
No.
It'll have to be a character I haven't done Greed on yet.
And I have done Greed on Esasel.
What other games are on the agenda?
Well, Minecraft is next month.
I'm actually moving next month, guys.
At the end of next month.
So, it's gonna be a little bit of Minecraft Season 3.
And then I'm gonna have a...
Like, maybe half a week or so.
Where I'm moving to another apartment.
And...
No streams in that period, of course.
But then I'll be back in a new setting.
It's a little bit of a bigger apartment.
Just so Jackie has more space to run on, you know.
And I can actually have room for a TV.
Because I don't have room for a TV where I live right now.
It's still kinda small.
But yeah.
No, it is July.
But I'm moving on the 1st of August.
Yeah, so I guess I should have said the beginning of August.
And not the end of July.
Meep's kitten.
I believe so.
I mean...
We know there's animals that practically live forever, right?
I don't see why science couldn't get us to that point.
I think it'll happen.
Maybe not in our lifetimes.
I hope it does.
Would be cool.
Would be nice to live forever, you know.
Get to see all the games that come out.
See how the universe ends.
Finally...
Be part of the...
Alien discovery one day, you know.
Discovering an alien signal from space.
That would be so freaking cool to...
Be a part of, you know.
Or just witness the world getting killed by AI.
Robots taking over, you know.
Little nano-robots flying all over.
Poisoning us.
I mean, of all the ways to go out, that's pretty cool.
Imagine dying to a robot uprising.
That's much cooler than dying of some ulcer.
Or cancer.
Right?
It would be kind of hype.
If I'm gonna die...
Let it be from a robot uprising.
Or an alien invasion.
Or zombies?
It's not as cool.
Zombies are kind of yesterday, aren't they?
Ha ha ha ha!
What do you think about the next tainted character's gonna be?
Um...
Well, whatever character that I fight the key on, I guess.
I don't know.
It'll have to be up to the RNG gods up there.
But I would...
I would assume maybe Isaac?
Yeah, probably Isaac.
If I had to guess.
Zombies are scary, because what if the person is still in there?
Yeah, now I'm thinking about a movie I saw recently.
A horror movie.
If I recall, it was a horror film.
Ha ha ha ha!
You know the one.
Makes me think of that one.
If the whole world population went into a battle royale, what place would you get?
Oh, you mean like on the leaderboards?
Nah, I would be one of the first to die.
I have the survival instincts of a turtle.
Literally, I will just sit in my house, bar the doors, until they break in and kill me.
I can't fight.
I don't know how to survive out in the wild.
I'm totally and utterly reliant on modern civilization.
Like, when I don't have a dishwasher, I panic.
That's where I'm at in life.
That's a good strat, though.
I guess it is.
Maybe I could fish.
Nutrient myself with some good old fish?
I mean, how hard can it be?
I mean, Gollum just picks him out of the water with his hands.
I can do that.
Maybe spearfishing or something?
Or maybe I'll go bow hunting.
Ha ha ha ha!
This is totally not gonna happen, by the way.
I can't do any of that.
I need a new body.
I would like to become a robot.
Right?
People with disabilities would probably fucking welcome getting a bionic armor.
Or something.
We're moving closer to Cyberpunk 2077.
I saw a video on YouTube of a girl who didn't have a right arm.
And she had, like, a bionic arm.
And it looked cool as hell.
I think that looked so badass, you know?
It's probably really annoying to deal with.
But just from a looks perspective, it looked badass.
Yes.
Yeah.
Particularly a new neck, because that's causing my body to malfunction.
Oh man, that sucks.
What happened?
Was it, like, some kind of accident, or has it always been like that?
Man, that sucks ass.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You'd replace your lower body with a monocycle?
How are you gonna do the 12 steps, then?
Oh, wait.
No, no, wait.
The 12 steps are related to alcohol, right?
IRL survival stream to gather the ingredients for the cooking stream.
Dude, it's not...
It's not gonna be fun.
I'm gonna be standing there, just not knowing what to do, and go, I'm cold, I wanna go home.
Accident in life?
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Good news, though.
I mean, science and technology is freaking accelerating at an insane pace right now.
In part, thanks to AI as well.
Like, everything is coming together right now to just give us insane development.
So, who knows what's gonna happen in the near future.
You know?
I mean, I saw a video on YouTube of someone who was completely, completely paralyzed throughout the entire body.
And they had, like, some...
Was it Neuralink or some other company?
Where they were able to control, like, a computer, at least, via their brain.
You know?
Like, that's...
That's crazy.
And this is just the start of it.
It's gonna get better and better.
What about gathering the ingredients for the meth cooking stream?
You mean, like, just going on the dark web and ordering illegal-ass stuff?
I don't think I'd go out into the wild and collect whatever I need to make meth.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know if it works like that.
I've never made meth.
You don't buy everything in one place.
Oh, that's true!
That's some good advice right there.
Spread it out.
Yep.
I saw someone play chess with their mind.
Isn't everyone playing chess with their mind?
You think about it?
Ha ha.
What do you think about daily challenges?
It's basically set seat runs as 100% save and resets each day.
Yeah, that could be fun, actually, at some point.
I think I've gotten to the point where maybe we could do that.
Just to see, you know?
What do you guys think?
Do you agree?
Should we try and do some set seat runs, the challenges, daily challenges, or no?
Dailies do have every item unlocked.
Right.
All you'd be seeing are items you haven't seen.
But what do you mean?
I've already unlocked so many items.
There's no way.
I would be seeing mostly the items I've already discovered, right?
With some extra ones.
Wait, some items need daily runs to be completed to unlock?
Really?
You have, like, 2% of the items?
That's just a lie, Lizard King.
I don't believe that at all.
I would actually bet my life on that being wrong.
I would lay down my life.
Wager my life.
I'd say you'd be...
Oh, wait.
Guys, 2% of the game is insane.
Come on, be real.
That is just not true.
How long has it been since I've seen a new map in the game?
Like, 15 streams or something.
There's no way I've seen only 3% of the game.
That makes no sense.
Wait, let me see.
So, achievements on Binding Visek.
I have 238 out of 641.
That means I've completed at least 30% of the game.
Boom.
30% is complete.
It's right there.
Black on white.
Well, more like white on bluish.
But you know what I mean.
Yeah, that's fair, I think.
But there you go.
Yeah, it's still a long...
Okay.
Guys, it's time for me to eat.
It's getting late.
It was a late stream.
Thanks for watching.
And guys, if you haven't checked out the XCOM videos on YouTube yet...
Boy, you gotta check them out, man.
XCOM is becoming one of my favorite games of all time.
I'm not even kidding.
If you haven't played the game yet, I urge you to play it.
And then go watch the Let's Play.
You gotta play XCOM, okay?
I'm telling you.
I'm a little late to the party with it, but you gotta play it.
It is insane.
Okay, I'll see you around.
Bye-bye.